Guide to the Joy Golden Papers, 1956-2012 RL.00461
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1979-2005 and undated, 13 boxes
  - Audition tapes
    - Caldor Group: Guys and Clerk. 1996. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV9)
    - Caldor Group: English and Hispanic. 1996. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00, 2 tapes (Box AV9)
    - Canada Dry. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 60:00, 4 tapes (Box AV9)
    - Canadian casting. 1985. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV9)
    - Candy Kisses. 1995. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV9)
    - Capalbos Fruit Baskets: Bribe; Mr. Cheap. 1995. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV9)
    - Care Choices HMO. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 16:00 (Box AV9)
    - Carefree Sugarless Gum: Announcer voices. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV9)
    - Carefree Sugarless Gum auditions. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV9)
    - Carlsberg: Shrink. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV9)
    - Carnival Air Lines: Warm-up Guy. 1995. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV9)
    - Casual Corner demo: Blind Date. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV9)
    - Catskills on Broadway. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV9)
    - Catskills on Broadway. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 4:00 (Box AV9)
    - CBS: Maharishi Ben. 1987. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV9)
    - CBS: Rajah Ben. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV9)
    - Cheerwine auditions. 1988. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV9)
    - Cheerwine: Emerson and Me. 1988. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 0:30 (Box AV9)
    - Cheerwine: Major Zero voiceover. 1988. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 0:30, 2 tapes (Box AV9)
    - Choice Care: If Your Head Hurts; Lake Ronkokomo. 1990. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 10:00 (Box AV9)
    - Clairol: Therapist; Mother; Jealousy. 1993. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV9)
    - Clairol voiceover. 1997. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV9)
    - Coca-Cola: Tall Tale. 1988. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00, 2 tapes (Box AV9)
    - Coca-Cola: There Goes the Gang; Telephone Call. 1988. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV9)
    - Cohen's Fashion Optical auditions. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV9)
    - Cohen's Fashion Optical: Personals. 1987. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00, 6 tapes (Box AV9)
    - Cohen's Fashion Optical: Red Glasses. 1987. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00, 2 tapes (Box AV9)
    - Cohen's Fashion Optical: Shopping. 1987. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV9)
    - Comedy Tonight: It's Not Funny; Laugh, Herm. 1994. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV9)
    - Coors announcers. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00, 3 tapes (Box AV9)
    - Cutter Insect Repellent: Tour; Wedding. 1992-1993. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV9)
    - Cutter Insect Repellent: Tour. 1993. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV9)
    - Dairy Farmers Association. 1988. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00, 2 tapes (Box AV9)
    - Death Defying Acts. 1994. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV9)
    - Dixan Detergent: Senator. 1986. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV9)
    - Dunkin Donuts auditions. 1994. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00, 2 tapes (Box AV9)
    - Dunkin Donuts scratch tracks. 1994. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 4:00 (Box AV9)
    - Dunkin Donuts: Wendell. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00, 2 tapes (Box AV9)
    - E-Loan. 2000. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV9)
    - Elephant Malt Liquor: Stranger; Lawn Party; Med School; Surprise; Kloster. 1986. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 15:00, 2 tapes (Box AV9)
    - Empire Kosher Chicken: Uncle Morty. 1993. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00, 2 tapes (Box AV9)
    - Equitable Industrial. 1994. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00, 2 tapes (Box AV9)
    - Enterprise Rent-a-Car animatic voiceover. 1997. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV9)
    - Enterprise Rent-a-Car audition. 1991. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV9)
    - Enterprise Rent-a-Car: Honeymoon; Accident. 1994. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV9)
    - Enterprise Rent-a-Car: Phone loopa. 1997. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV9)
    - Enterprise Rent-a-Car: Ringo; Baby. 1997. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV9)
    - Enterprise Rent-a-Car selects. 1997. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV9)
    - Fair. 1991. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV9)
    - Family Counseling Services: Child Abuse; Family Violence; Lanie. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV9)
    - Felix Van Djik: Ringo. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV9)
    - First Florida: Banker/Spoon; Liar. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV9)
    - First Florida: Ring; Liar; Fairy Tale; Wedding. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 4:00, 2 tapes (Box AV9)
    - First Florida: Storyteller. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV9)
    - First Florida: Storyteller; Bride. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 6:00 (Box AV9)
    - First Florida: Storytellers and Tortoises. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV9)
    - First Florida: Wedding; Fairy Tale; Ring; Liar. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 4:00 (Box AV9)
    - First Florida: Yuppie Brides and Grooms. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV9)
    - First Investors: The Thinker; Dentist; Investment Course; Home Movies. 1986. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 5:00 (Box AV9)
    - Fleischmann's auditions. 1991. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 5:00, 2 tapes (Box AV9)
    - Fox Video. 1991. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV9)
    - FPL auditions. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 19:00 (Box AV9)
    - FPL: Older Couple; Dog; Storm; Tree. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 6:00 (Box AV9)
    - FPL: Older Couple; Tree. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV9)
    - Frosty Paws: Nutritionist. 1988. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV9)
    - Frosty Paws: Session. 1988. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV9)
    - Frosty Paws: Stanley. 1988. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV9)
    - Geico announcers. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 10:00 (Box AV9)
    - Geico auditions. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV9)
    - Geico casting. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 20:00 (Box AV9)
    - Geico selects. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 10:00, 2 tapes (Box AV9)
    - General Tire: XP2000V; Grabber AT. 1987. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV9)
    - Genie Garage Door Opener: The Pro. 1988. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV9)
    - Genesee Beer: Bonding; Birthday. 1996. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV9)
    - Genny Light Beer: Poker Game; Game Show. 1996. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV9)
    - Goldstar Microwave Oven: Rich Couple. 1986. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00, 2 tapes (Box AV9)
    - Grey Entertainment: Late Nite Comic. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV9)
    - Grey Entertainment: The Actor. 1987. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00, 4 tapes (Box AV9)
    - Haagen Dazs demos. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV9)
    - Haagen Dazs: Flavor of the Year. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV9)
    - Haagen Dazs: Rendezvous. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00, 2 tapes (Box AV9)
    - Hallmark: Easter; Father's Day. 1987. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV10)
    - Healthcare Solutions. 1999. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV10)
    - Hoffman La Roche: Whitehall cough syrup abuse. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 4:00, 2 tapes (Box AV10)
    - Hornsby's Pub Cider: Widder Lady; Bear Trap; Dixie Lee. 1996. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV10)
    - Hughes. 2001. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 11:00 (Box AV10)
    - IC Beer auditions. 1991. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00, 2 tapes (Box AV10)
    - Interwest Savings: Nostalgia. 1987. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV10)
    - Jeffery Modell Foundation. 2005. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 5:00 (Box AV10)
    - JobDirect.com. 2000. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV10)
    - Joy Radio: 13 Golden Classics. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 13:00 (Box AV10)
    - Joy Radio demo reel. 2000. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 7:00 (Box AV10)
    - Joy Radio: Golden Oldies and Newies. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 15:00, 3 tapes (Box AV10)
    - KABC: Haunted Halloween. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV10)
    - KABC: Haunted House. 1987. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV10)
    - KABC: Shrink. 1987. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV10)
    - KPIX auditions. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV10)
    - KPIX: Affair. 1988. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV10)
    - KPIX: Bust. 1988. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV10)
    - KPIX: Mall Talk; Old Man; Old Woman. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV10)
    - KPIX: Pig. 1988. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV10)
    - KPIX: Reed Sweeney. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV10)
    - KYW-TV: Guy; woman; Creatures of Habit. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV10)
    - KYW-TV: Therapy Group; Charles; Cynthia. 1990. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 4:00 (Box AV10)
    - Ladies' Home Journal: Aunt Nilda; Good Old Boy; Sybil. 1987. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV10)
    - Ladies' Home Journal: Aunt Nilda; Pop; Sybil. 1987. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV10)
    - Ladies' Home Journal: Dotty Schott. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV10)
    - Ladies' Home Journal: Ellen Sue Druckett. 1987. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00, 2 tapes (Box AV10)
    - Ladies' Home Journal: Jasamine. 1987. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV10)
    - Levi's: (1) Bakelite; Sax. 1990. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00, 2 tapes (Box AV10)
    - Levi's: (2) Bakelite; Leica; Sax. 1990. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00, 2 tapes (Box AV10)
    - Levi's: (3) Leica. 1990. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00, 2 tapes (Box AV10)
    - Levi's: (4) Announcers. 1990. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV10)
    - Levi's: (5) Mechanic. 1990. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV10)
    - Levi's: (6) Journalist. 1990. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV10)
    - Levi's: (7) Surfer. 1990. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV10)
    - Levi's 501: Announcer; Mechanic; Remington; Surf. 1990. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 45:00 (Box AV10)
    - Levi's 501: Car Buff. 1990. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV10)
    - Levi's 501: Leica; Sax; Bakelite. 1990. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 45:00 (Box AV10)
    - Levi's recasting: Bakelite; Strat; Tags. 1990. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 60:00, 3 tapes (Box AV10)
    - Lifesavers: Wild Recipe. 1993. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 14:00 (Box AV10)
    - Lifesavers callbacks. 1993. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 13:00 (Box AV10)
    - Lightpath. 2000. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00, 2 tapes (Box AV10)
    - Lincoln Mercury/American Service Center: 4th of July; Brothers in Law. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00, 2 tapes (Box AV10)
    - Lysol: Rod Serling. 1997. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV10)
    - Lysol: Who's Got It?; Cold Bug. 1997. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV10)
    - Marcus James. 1988. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 4:00, 2 tapes (Box AV10)
    - Mastercard. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV10)
    - Matchline. 1994. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV10)
    - Mateus. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV10)
    - Mateus: Slumsleys; Commitment; Sun Su. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV10)
    - MCI. 1993. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 4:00 (Box AV10)
    - MCI. 1995. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV10)
    - Meadowlands: Boys' Nite; Friday Nite Out; Anniversary. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV10)
    - Medi-Quick. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV10)
    - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Foundation: Healthcare men and women. 1995. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV10)
    - Midas. 1995. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV10)
    - Milkbone: Best Buddy; Perfect Guy; Wet Nose; What an Animal. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 6:00 (Box AV10)
    - Money Magazine 4 spots. 1984. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 4:00 (Box AV10)
    - Money Magazine: Taxes; Anniversary; Dentist; Avoidance. 1984. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 4:00, 2 tapes (Box AV10)
    - Money Magazine: Taxes; Anniversary; Subscription; Dentist; Avoidance. 1984. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 6:00 (Box AV10)
    - Monmouth Park. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00, 2 tapes (Box AV10)
    - MTA: Beach. 2001. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV10)
    - MTA: Holiday. 2001. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV10)
    - MTA: Improvements. 2002. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV10)
    - MTA: MVM radio; Convenience TV. 1999. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00, 2 tapes (Box AV10)
    - MTA: Santa and Reindeer. 2001. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV10)
    - MTA Industrial: Progress in Motion. 2002. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 6:00, 2 tapes (Box AV10)
    - MTA Metrocard: Predictions. 2002. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV10)
    - MTA Spanish versions. 2000. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 6:00 (Box AV10)
    - National Gas: Dryer; Furnace. 1990. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV10)
    - NBC: Adele Writes to Phil; Big Change; Concierge; Ma and audrey. 1990. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 4:00, 2 tapes (Box AV10)
    - NBC: Phil Donohue. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00, 5 tapes (Box AV10)
    - NEC Computers. 1996. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV10)
    - Nescafe. 1994. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00, 2 tapes (Box AV10)
    - Nestlé Sweet Success: Getting Ahead; Empowerment; Joan's Story; Friends. 1995. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 8:00 (Box AV10)
    - Nestlé Sweet Success: Joan's Story; Announcers. 1995. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 9:00 (Box AV10)
    - Nivea: Boys; Moving; Bathtime. 1990. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV10)
    - Nivea composite. 1990. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 6:00 (Box AV10)
    - North Fork Bank.1994-1998. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00, 5 tapes (Box AV10)
    - North Fork Bank: Extra Faulkners. 1996. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV10)
    - North Fork Bank: Henry Hudson. 1999. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 7:00 (Box AV10)
    - North Fork Bank: LI Whiners. 1994. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 20:00 (Box AV10)
    - North Fork Bank: Memo; Relationships. 1997. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 7:00 (Box AV10)
    - North Fork Bank: Press Conference. 1999. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 12:00 (Box AV10)
    - North Fork Bank: Stanley. 1997. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 13:00 (Box AV10)
    - Northwest Natural Gas: Cure for Procrastination; Mona. 1994. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 10:00 (Box AV10)
    - NY State Farm Products. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV10)
    - NY Style Bagel Chips: Anniversary; Cocktail Party; Frankie. 1995. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 8:00 (Box AV10)
    - Ohio Wines: Announcers. 1988. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV10)
    - Ohio Wines: Georgia; LA LA; NY NY. 1988. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV10)
    - Old Tyme Soft Drinks. 1990. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 4:00 (Box AV10)
    - Opti-Free Lens Care: Monti and Harris takes. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 4:00 (Box AV10)
    - Opti-Free Lens Care: Opera. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV10)
    - Opti-Free Lens Care: Superwoman; Gridlock; Mother; Date. 1993. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 12:00, 2 tapes (Box AV10)
    - Opti-Free Lens Care: VCR. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV10)
    - Partnership for a Drug Free America: Casting. 1998. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00, 6 tapes (Box AV10)
    - Partnership for a Drug Free America: Lanie's Wedding; Mickey. 1987. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV10)
    - Partnership for a Drug Free America: Mickey; Lanie's Wedding; Joey's Party. 1987. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV10)
    - Partnership for a Drug Free America: Perfect Guy; Lanie's Wedding. 1987. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV10)
    - Pealer's Flowers: 2000 Carats; Chance Meeting. 1991. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV10)
    - Pealer's Flowers: Pop; Shrink; Friends. 1991. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV10)
    - Pedone: Sweet & Low; Butter Buds. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 15:00 (Box AV10)
    - PHS Healthcare: Spelunker; Huddle; On Hold. 1992-1993. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00, 2 tapes (Box AV10)
    - Pickles: State Fair. 1993. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 20:00 (Box AV10)
    - Pitney Bowes: Dr. Overcharge. 1987. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00, 3 tapes (Box AV10)
    - Precious Cheese: Neighbors. 1996. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 5:00 (Box AV10)
    - Precious Cheese: Theresa; Mrs. Capanari; Angela. 1996. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 4:00 (Box AV10)
    - Precious Cheese: Store owner campaign. 1996. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV10)
    - Pringles: Guru; What's the Difference?: Young Guy. 1996. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00, 2 tapes (Box AV10)
    - Ragu: I Like That; You Had It, Lou; I Don't Care. 1990. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00, 2 tapes (Box AV10)
    - Ragu: Mom the Victor. 1990. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 6:00 (Box AV10)
    - Ralston Purina: Fathers. 1988. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV10)
    - Ralston Purina: Jealousy. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV10)
    - Rave: Create and Control. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV10)
    - R.C. Wiley's: Old Couch. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV10)
    - Regina Porter Clothes: Spiritual Awakening. 1994. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV10)
    - Restaurant Association: Final casting. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00, 2 tapes (Box AV10)
    - Restaurant Association: Russians; Announcers; Women. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV10)
    - Restaurant Association: Women. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00, 2 tapes (Box AV10)
    - Riscassi & Davis. 1991. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00, 3 tapes (Box AV10)
    - Riscassi & Davis: Spokesperson and testimonials. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 6:00 (Box AV11)
    - Riscassi & Davis: Spokeswoman. 1993. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 5:00 (Box AV11)
    - Riscassi & Davis: Tough World; Security. 1991. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 5:00 (Box AV11)
    - Riscassi & Davis: Why Advertise?. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV11)
    - Rivendell. 1991. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00, 3 tapes (Box AV11)
    - Roy Rogers. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00, 4 tapes (Box AV11)
    - Saks Fifth Avenue. 1994. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 9:00 (Box AV11)
    - Savings Bank of Manchester. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 4:00 (Box AV11)
    - Seagrams: The Lodge; Dear John. 1995. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 8:00 (Box AV11)
    - Seagrams Fruit Coolers. 1995. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV11)
    - Shell ETD. 1994. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 5:00 (Box AV11)
    - Shell/Formula Shell. 1995. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00, 8 tapes (Box AV11)
    - Shell Gasoline. 1994. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 19:00 (Box AV11)
    - Shell Rotella Oil. 1993. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 17:00, 2 tapes (Box AV11)
    - Shoe Town: Friends; Arthur. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV11)
    - SNET annou ncer. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV11)
    - SNET: I Seen It. 1994. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 8:00, 3 tapes (Box AV11)
    - SNET: Klinger and Hanger. 1987. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV11)
    - SNET: Laslo. 1995. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 18:00, 2 tapes (Box AV11)
    - SNET: Merv and Harv. 1986. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV11)
    - SNET: Piano; Yella Umbrella; Talking Dog. 1987. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV11)
    - SNET: Shower; How Many?; Barb's Gift; Getting Late. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 12:00 (Box AV11)
    - S.O.S. Soap Pads: Einstein; Bright Eyes. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV11)
    - Sterling Jewelers. 1988. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV11)
    - Sundance: Widder Lady; Bear Trap; Dixie Lee. 1991. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 3:00 (Box AV11)
    - Sunkist: See Ya; Dreaming. 1995. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV11)
    - Supercharger: Wedding. 1994. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV11)
    - TGI Fridays: Eardrum. 1997. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV11)
    - The Avenue: Talk of the Avenue. 1990. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV11)
    - Thighmaster Plus. 1993. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV11)
    - Today Show: Who's Running/Bush. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV11)
    - Tri-Honda. 1991. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV11)
    - Tri-Star: Short Circuit II. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV11)
    - Tropical Freezes: Anniversary. 1996. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00, 2 tapes (Box AV11)
    - Tropical Freezes: Anniversary; Ma's Visit. 1995. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV11)
    - USA Network: Maharishi Ben. 1987. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00, 4 tapes (Box AV11)
    - USA Network: Shrink. 1987. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV11)
    - USA Network: Woody Allen. 1987. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00, 8 tapes (Box AV11)
    - V8 Juice. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00, 2 tapes (Box AV11)
    - V8 Juice: Race Track; Auctioneer. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV11)
    - Volvic Water. 1994. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00, 4 tapes (Box AV11)
    - Volvic Water: Shrinking World. 1994. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV11)
    - Waldbaum's. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV11)
    - Waldbaum's: Shirl #1. 1995. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV11)
    - Waldenbooks. 1988. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV11)
    - Warnaco: Asian television voiceovers. 1995. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV11)
    - Warnaco: Buy Two Get One Free; Dear Ma. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:30 (Box AV11)
    - Warnaco: If You Were; Friends. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV11)
    - Warnaco: Just Your Fit. 1991. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV11)
    - Warnaco: Speedo Fitness Center. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV11)
    - Warner's Just Your Fit: Right Here Right Now. 1991. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV11)
    - Warner's and Olga Panty Sale. 1992. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV11)
    - WBIS-TV 31. 1997. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV11)
    - Wee Three Records. 1991. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV11)
    - Weight Watchers: Oompah. 1991. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00, 4 tapes (Box AV11)
    - Western Beef. 1995. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV11)
    - WFSB: Oprah Winfree Show. Undated. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 2:00 (Box AV11)
    - Whitehall/Hoffman La Roche Cough Syrup Abuse PSA: Dear Eddie. 1991. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 1:00 (Box AV11)
    - Winkelman's. 1997. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV11)
    - Wild Turkey. 1989. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00, 3 tapes (Box AV11)
    - Wilmington Trust. 1999. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV11)
    - Wilmington Trust: Copier. 2002. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV11)
    - Wilmington Trust: Skippy. 2002. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV11)
    - WNBC: Love Connection; Ruckus. 1991. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00, 2 tapes (Box AV11)
    - WordPerfect. 1993. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00 (Box AV11)
    - Workbench: What's a Workbench?. 1996. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00, 3 tapes (Box AV11)
    - WRC: Family Feud. 1990. Format: Audiocassette. TRT: 30:00, 2 tapes (Box AV11)